http://www.ovpb.net/sites/ovpb/privacy-policy

Menu
HomeGame SchedulesCalendarPONY About PONY2018 USA Baseball Bat StandardLeague Info About UsBoard MembersContact UsDivisions & Age CriteriaGovernance & Rules By-LawsLocal RulesPitching Rules - Pitch Smart GuidelinesConcussion Safety TrainingCode of ConductTerms of School UsageChannels of CommunicationRefund PolicyPony NationalLocationsTim Anderson Memorial FieldNewsPrograms Sign Up! CurrentUpcomingSpring BallFall BallSelectAll-StarsSponsorship Team Sponsorship RequirementDownloads
Privacy Policy
The Orangevale PONY Baseball Privacy Policy has been written to answer questions you might have about this issue. As a youth organization we are very concerned about privacy. Therefore, we have taken measures to tailor our content and offerings to help protect an individual’s privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to information collected on Orangevale PONY Baseball authored websites such as: www.ovpb.net and our official pages on Facebook and other social media networks as well as information received from other sources such as charter enrollment and player records reporting.Our Commitment to SecurityOrangevale PONY Baseball, Incorporated has implemented physical, electronic and managerial processes to safeguard the privacy of the information it obtains.Advice to Children and ParentsWe strongly advise children to get their parent(s) or guardian(s) to review any information they intend to transmit and get their permission before submitting any kind of personal data to anyone over the Internet. We urge parents to repeatedly discuss with their children the danger of giving personal information to anyone (online or in person)whom they don’t personally know. We also encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children monitoring and reviewing their children’s online activity. As a policy, no person under the age of 13 is permitted to register directly to receive Orangevale PONY Baseball’s electronic communications.What personal information do we collect for our electronic database?Complete data for all players, managers/coaches and league officers is required. Player registration data must include the date of birth of the player and parent or guardian contact information.How do we use personal information collected and received?Any information gathered by Orangevale PONY Baseball on this website (ovpb.net), through the Orangevale PONY Baseball Registration and Coach/Manager registration process and/or by any other means, will be used for the purpose of furthering the mission of Orangevale PONY Baseball, Incorporated. Orangevale PONY Baseball, Incorporated does not sell any information collected from you to outside companies. On occasion, we may provide special offers or services through Orangevale PONY Baseball, Incorporated and/or its sponsors, licensees or other business associates. We also may use the information to fulfill your requests for information or products or to respond to your inquiries about our program. We may use this information to communicate with you, such as to update you on new rules, regulations or risk management issues, ask your opinion through surveys and research, notify you that you have won a contest, or provide you with the latest news story being covered by Orangevale PONY Baseball. The information you provide in connection with our website and email communications, online forums, social media sites and communities is used to create an interactive experience. We may use this information to facilitate conversation and from time to time, offer you information, programs and services. Should you receive information from Orangevale PONY Baseball or one of our partners, this information will be clearly identified with Orangevale PONY Baseball identification marks in adherence with our trademark registration. The data provided to Orangevale PONY Baseball is utilized by Orangevale PONY Baseball in the ways such as the following:To catalog and record each individual player into a yearly listing of participants in the Orangevale PONY Baseball program. This information may also be used for operational issues that may arise with respect to eligibility of the participants in our all-star program.To maintain a record of the coaches and managers involved in the Orangevale PONY Baseball program and their associated team and/or league. This information is used to provide seasonal training materials, to send the PONY Magazine for their team’s players during the season as well as operational issues that may arise requiring contact with Orangevale PONY Baseball.Email addresses provided to Orangevale PONY Baseball through the league player record sharing process by each player’s parent(s) or guardian(s), and coach and/or manager are incorporated into Orangevale PONY Baseball electronic database for the current season. Individuals receive an “Opt-In” welcome announcement and are given the choice to opt-in to receive communications from Orangevale PONY Baseball. Every communication sent will provide you an option to “Opt-Out”.Household mailing addresses reported by leagues are occasionally used to provide information to those residents about the Orangevale PONY Baseball program. Should information be sent, it will be sent under the cover of “Current Resident” or “To the Parent or Guardian of Orangevale PONY Baseball Participant.” The privacy policy below describes our process for collecting and using email addresses of our constituents.At Orangevale PONY Baseball, we collect information in addition to player registration data and coach/manager data in order to help identify you and/ or your child’s interests in the Orangevale PONY Baseball program and the associated local league with which you may be affiliated. On our websites and through our various links to resources and information, you can read articles, enter contests, participate in promotions, express your opinion, shop online or subscribe to our online portals, emails and newsletters. On occasion, we may ask for personal contact information from you for purposes such as:to provide you with information that you've requested based on your selected preferences upon Opt-In;to enable us to respond to your inquiry;to register you for a contest or promotion;to take your subscription for a Orangevale PONY Baseball publication or web-based portal, or;for league operation and education.You also have the opportunity to “Opt-Out” of any Orangevale PONY Baseball controlled electronic large group communication at any time by sending an email to at webmaster@ovpb.net and typing Unsubscribe in the subject line or by clicking on the Opt-Out link at the bottom of any email you receive from us.Please note that some information you receive may direct you to a non-Orangevale PONY Baseball website. Please refer to these websites for specific Privacy Policies and use of data as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. We may be required to share your personal information and non-personal information pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants, or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use, disclose, and/or share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Website’s Terms of Use or as otherwise required by law.Individual Submissions and PromotionsWe may offer coupons, special discounts, contests, games, and promotions on behalf of Orangevale PONY Baseball and/or our national partners; or invite you to submit stories, photos, comments, or questions to certain areas of our website. On these occasions, we may ask you to voluntarily submit additional information along with your submission so that we can notify you if you are a winner, or to respond to (or ask) questions.Cookies -- What are they?Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies make Internet surfing easier for you by saving your passwords and preferences while you’re at a site. The use of cookies is an industry standard -- you’ll find that they are used by most major websites. By showing how and when visitors use the site, cookies can also help website developers see which areas are popular and which are not.Does the Orangevale PONY Baseball website use cookies?Yes. As you browse ovpb.net or Orangevale PONY Baseball-owned websites, cookies or similar technology may be placed on your computer so that we can understand what information interests you on our site, in order to continue to provide information in the future. On occasion, we may provide target advertising through partners like AdRoll and Facebook to present you with additional information about our program and its offerings based on your previous interaction with ovpb.net. These techniques do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. We also work with third party companies to assist us with website analytics such as evaluating the use and operation of our website so that we can continue to enhance the website(s) and the information contained within.
Contact
Contact UsWeb Mail
Get Connected
Get the latest news
Site Powered by TeamSideline.com
Privacy
|
Admin Sign In
